🎵 Good morning, it is 9am and I went to bed so late last night
because I was finishing up a video but the video is done.
We have a lot of work to do today.
We are here because I'm filming a what I eat in a week video.
Show you guys some recent recipes that I've been eating a lot of that I've
been enjoying especially that it's the end of summer.
We have some really good produce right now So let's have some breakfast and move
on with the day and hopefully we'll come up with some fun things to eat
to inspire you to enjoy the last few summer weeks.
Recently, I've been kind of uninspired with breakfast.
So my most frequented meal in the last few weeks has been a mix of
scrambled eggs with different ingredients.
So today we've got a combination of chopped up chives and some feta cheese.
I also fried up some turkey bacon on the side and for the eggs It's
really easy to mix in anything pretty much you put the scrambled eggs in the
pan And then I topped it up with the chopped chives and then once the
eggs were almost done I added the feta cheese and I turned off the heat
and just kind of mix it all in together So the feta cheese melts a
little bit and incorporates into the eggs.
Well, then we plated everything I toasted some bread I've been really into this seedy
toast from trader joe's topped it up with some cream cheese and tomatoes because this
is just the ultimate toast combination in my opinion.
Always salt your tomatoes and that was pretty much breakfast.
Usually for breakfast you'll see in this video I have a rotation of different meals
that I make and it's usually something that has to do with scrambled eggs and
something on the side or I do a yogurt bowl with some fruit and some
my favorite granola that I make myself or I do a protein pancake.
So you'll probably see some of those in the video coming up and sometimes I'm
left feeling a little craving for something sweet and this time I made another cream
cheese toast with that seedy bread but topped it up with some peaches and a
little drizzle of honey and it was so good and fresh and really hit the
spot for a little something sweet after breakfast.
but my
video is live my thumbnail turned out way better than i expected somehow i always
figure it out but um i am going to head outside real quick i need
to get a few things from sephora because i just kind of like ran out
of skincare so i'm gonna go to sephora i also I'm gonna pick up some
packages on the way.
We're going to either make lunch or get lunch.
We still have so much to do and it is, what time is it, like
1 p.m.
Anyway, but let's head out, move along with the day.
Hello again, it's time to make lunch and I've been wanting to make this carrot
salad recipe.
It is a raw carrot salad that I've seen all over my Instagram and everybody's
reaction is making me want to try it.
So we're going to try it today.
I got some carrots specifically for this.
We're starting off with some chicken thighs that I seasoned with my usual Trader Joe's
onion salt that I use on most of my proteins.
a little extra salt because I don't find it salty enough and some black pepper
and I cooked the chicken thighs in a pan nothing crazy nothing special but the
star of the show is this carrot salad so I started off by first washing
the carrots and then also peeling the outer layer before I actually started making ribbons
out of the carrots and I just used the same peeler and I found that
it really helps putting it on some type of surface to help you support the
carrot.
I also chopped up some green onion to go into the salad later.
I did a combination of different sauces.
I followed one of the recipes I found online.
All the ingredients and measurements and everything will be listed down below in the description
for you guys.
But this came together quite quickly.
I would say the most time-consuming part was ribboning the carrots, especially because I did
quite a lot of them.
Then you mix in everything.
You add a good amount of sesame seeds if you like I like a lot
of them and I always toss a salad with my hands because I feel like
it gets the salad dressed the best way possible and then we plated everything
but here we are first taste
now it is really good it's very refreshing pretty easy to make a little bit
time consuming in terms of like slicing the carrots.
It's actually really good.
Hello everyone.
I just am having a snack right now.
This is a yellow kiwi.
I've never had a yellow kiwi until yesterday for the first time.
And you know I'm a person that eats pretty much everything.
There are very few things that I do not like.
But kiwis are one of those things that I just was like I'm not really
like I don't really get it.
It's like not really that good and it kind of like hurts my mouth a
little bit and I don't know and then I went to Trader Joe's the other
day I saw these kiwis and now I like kiwis like what is that especially
the yellow one I don't know how different the yellow one is I think this
is like sweeter than the green one
more sour but I'm a kiwi gal now all in one bite
It's so refreshing.
So good.
It's so
good.
Reporting live from the Lower East Side.
We also, I mean, I look like my face is wet because it is 90
degrees at 8pm.
I don't know what's going on, but we're on the Lower East Side.
We are waiting.
It's actually 86.
Oh, it's Excuse me.
It is 86 and we're waiting for some burritos at this new place called Sandal
North on the Lower East Side.
I saw it on my Instagram a few days ago and it looked amazing But
unfortunately, they're sold out of the carne asada So we got a chicken one and
a shrimp one so we shall see but they look incredible they look like the
the tortilla looks crazy so okay the burritos here i'm trying to not be like
hella cringe right now anyways cheers this is the shrimp
Mmm, yum!
It's so fresh!
You only have the accent, try this.
Ooh, it's got a nice spice.
It's good.
As I was just explaining earlier, this breakfast we are having protein pancakes, but I
decided to make them more kind of like a Swedish pancake where they're a little
bit flappier and bigger and thinner and we're going to serve them with some cherry
compote cherry sauce so i got the cherries in a pan with a little bit
of sugar and they're just cooking and reducing and getting nice and soft and then
for the protein pancakes i used the buttermilk protein pancake mix from trader joe's and
i just added more liquid to make them thinner and i also put together a
a little yogurt, maple syrup, and lemon zest, mixed it all together, and layered each
pancake one on top of the other.
We did pancake, yogurt on top, a little bit of that cherry compote, then another
pancake, yogurt, and so on.
This was made on a whim.
I've never had this recipe before, and it was crazy good.
Bye.
Mmm.
Oh my God.
I honestly didn't expect it to be this good.
The biggest thing here is the lemon zest in the yogurt.
Mmm.
I just got ready.
I finished refilming what I needed to refilm from yesterday.
I'm going to a coffee shop, one of my favorite coffee shops to work at
in Brooklyn.
And I'm meeting my friend Carolina.
They have one of my favorite lunch salads of all time.
I have to edit what I filmed earlier.
And I also need to get started on editing my friend Brenda's wedding video that
I filmed for them.
So yeah, let's head out.
As I mentioned, this is probably one of my favorite salads and bowls for lunch.
And unfortunately, it is their summer grain bowl.
So it is limited edition and it's probably going to get off the menu soon
So I decided that i'm going to recreate it for you guys and for myself
so that I can make it again I sliced up a few little tomatoes.
I also had these garlic black pepper almonds So I gave those a rough chop
as well since they have almonds in their recipe I cooked up some farro, which
is really easy It takes 10 minutes and added in some pesto and mixed it
into the farro Which is pretty much how I assume that they make theirs I
would probably wait to cool off the farro mine was still hot and then we
plated everything I took some Crispy greens and added this Vinaigrette that I had made
in my fridge added the pesto farro added some of those Tomatoes and then they
also have Marinated watermelon in the recipe.
I don't know what it's marinated in So I just added plain old cubed watermelon
that I cut up a few days ago top the green salad with some feta
I made some random chicken that I seasoned very simply and just tore it up
into little pieces added the almonds and that's pretty much the recipe and let me
tell you it turned out pretty close to the original and I will definitely be
repeating this recipe
Hi friends, update, it is now
8pm.
You gotta tell me when I'm gonna be on camera.
It's all about being handed, okay?
Yoni is going to the store because we need cheddar.
I've been working all day, literally just now I put my computer away.
Excuse me, we've been working.
We've been working.
But I am about to make what has been one of our savior slash repeat
meals because it's so good.
It's so satisfying.
It's so filling and nourishing and everything.
And it's not even groundbreaking.
It is steak taco bowls or burrito bowls or whatever you want to call them.
But it's basically steak with fajita vegetables, rice.
I'm going to make a pico de gallo, avocado, cheddar, sour cream just the works
everything in a big bowl and you just go to town so that's exactly what
i need right now and that's what we're gonna make this is nothing crazy a
pretty straightforward recipe that i have been constantly making for yoni and i on evenings
where we just want to eat good and want a meal to come together quickly
so i am slicing up some bell peppers i usually like to have a mix
of colors but I only had orange.
Also sliced up some onion and then I actually bought specifically some grass-fed beef that
was already sliced and sprinkled some taco seasoning on top and I like to do
this before putting it in the pan.
I tried both methods and I feel like this one gets the beef better flavor
and better charring and then I cooked everything in separate pans so it cooks a
little bit faster and while those were on the stove I started making my pico
de gallo which was just some roughly chopped red onion, also roughly chopped tomatoes, and
some cilantro.
I like my salsa or pico de gallo very chunky, especially for this recipe.
And don't forget, very important, you have to use lime juice, not lemon, a little
bit of salt, and olive oil.
Then I combined the beef and the vegetables together so the vegetables also get that
flavor and plated my bowl.
I did a little bit of white rice at the bottom, put on that steak
and the vegetables, added some black beans straight out of the can, some cheddar cheese.
I add a lot of the pico de gallo.
Also added some avocado and some sour cream.
It's so good.
And it's perfect for meal prepping as well.
My little bowl.
I load this baby up good.
I've been eating these like on repeat.
It's been a core meal for us.
Mmm.
Good morning.
Another gloomy day.
Today calls for a cozy breakfast, okay?
That is savory.
A polenta breakfast bowl.
I've made polenta bowls many, many times before in these videos, but this was a
new combination.
We are boiling two eggs, soft boil seven minutes.
We also are frying up some turkey bacon and we're making the polenta.
I make the polenta a single serving in the microwave because it's just way easier.
A cup of water to a quarter cup of polenta and you mix it in
and you cook it for about five minutes and then you take it out and
mix it and then you put it back in if it needs more time.
I like to mix some cheddar cheese or some type of cheese in my polenta
and it kind of makes it a little bit of a grits vibe.
Then I basically plated everything.
This comes together so quickly, especially because the eggs and the turkey bacon are cooking
on their own.
And then you make the polenta.
Everything comes together so fast.
I chopped up the turkey bacon into little bits so it's easier to eat in
the bowl.
I also added some feta and some chopped chives.
Always remember to put salt and pepper on top of your boiled eggs.
It's all the difference.
And then on a whim, I decided to add some of this Trader Joe's hot
honey sauce.
And it was a game changer.
Guys, this is one of the best ones I've ever made.
It's so simple.
It's so good.
And the game changer, this Trader Joe's spicy honey sauce.
Wow.
I randomly decided to put this on and I was a little bit skeptical that
it might not be good.
But it is amazing.
I just got my bag all packed up.
I'm gonna go grab a coffee real quick and go work from the conference room
downstairs.
I have to edit the wedding video, have to get that done.
There's a lot of footage that I got to go through, but I'm just not
comfortable like doing it in our apartment because like we don't have stools yet and
it's just not that comfortable to like be on the couch the whole time, especially
because we don't even have a table that works.
We're also gonna have to record the podcast at some point today we were going
to record it on a Wednesday and today it's Friday so we didn't do that
it's just we're trying to pre-record uh one two three four five six seven eight
episodes before we leave for a trip which is in basically a week and a
half
for lunch we are making a nicoise salad or at least a version of it
we're starting off by quickly pickling some red onion sliced it added it to a
jar macerated it with a good amount of salt poured in a good amount of
vinegar and some hot water and the hot water is a must instead of cold
water because it will help break down the onion and pickle it faster then i
got some asparagus going in a pan to just sizzle it and cook it down
a little bit and then i made this red wine vinaigrette again all the measurements
and everything are going to be listed in the description for you to follow this
vinaigrette is the first time that i made it and it was so good simple
pretty basic stuff that i think everyone has in their fridge anyways and if you
make a bigger amount you can have it in the fridge and just use it
on different things throughout the week and then i plated everything on a bed of
crispy lettuce topped it off with the asparagus some boiled potatoes the red onion and
some flaky tuna this tuna is specifically that comes in a jar called Tanino, I
think.
This is a must because that tuna quality is incredible.
And then drizzled on top some of that red wine vinaigrette.
Just made lunch.
I tried to recreate the salad that I had when we went to Seattle.
It's a kind of like a niçoise salad.
I had a really good one when we went to Seattle so I was craving
that little bite of everything.
Mmm.
That's actually really good.
Good morning and happy Saturday.
We are gonna make breakfast.
I have some leftover rice, I have some kimchi, I have eggs.
We're going to make some kimchi fried rice.
I mean, you know, is it fried rice or do I just call the fried
rice that is to be determined by other people that know how to make proper
fried rice but that's what i call it because it's like you want to make
it with leftover rice you fry it up in a pan so you know that's
just this recipe is really simple and straightforward and i love it i can't believe
i haven't talked about this recipe before because i used to make it all the
time but you take a good amount of kimchi however much your heart desires and
give it a good chop i like mine pretty small and then you just cook
it in a pan with a little bit of sesame oil for that extra flavor
and you let it basically sweat out the water and get a little bit crispy
and get a little bit cooked and then you add your leftover rice cook that
in mix it all in and then you're going to add some scrambled eggs and
push everything to the side and let the scrambled eggs scramble on their own before
you mix it in with the rest of the before you mix it in with
the rest of the rice And I also drizzle in a little bit of tamari
or soy sauce, whatever you prefer.
To add it in a bowl, topped it up with a little bit of green
onion.
And I like to add a good heaping amount of fresh kimchi on top.
This is a great kimchi recipe to get in all of your probiotics nice and
early in the morning.
I just got ready.
I am going to bike over to Manhattan and I think I want to go
to La Cabra.
I've been meaning to have some time to continue reading my book that I started
last week and I just like haven't had the time.
So I'm going to bike over and I just really want to find a good
spot to read for a little bit.
How are you today?
I got a coffee.
I got an iced cappuccino with regular milk.
and I made my way to Union Square Market because the Farmer's Market is happening
today and I actually want to get a few things for lunch for when we
go back home.
But for now, I got two things.
One, I've had four and it was surprisingly so good.
Like I got it on a whim because I needed to spend $5 to pay with
card in one place.
And I got this almond pergamum little cake.
And I also got this little plum tart
That's like such a delicate flavor
That is so good I'm gonna try to like recreate this
Thank you.
So Yoni is on his way to meet me here and then we'll go home
together.
But I wanted to grab some bread, some cheese and some tomatoes for lunch
because I'm really craving something specific.
And we're at the farmer's market.
We gotta get the good tomatoes
Tomatoes from two different vendors.
I got some very beautifully aged cheddar.
I love a good sharp aged cheddar This is really good kind of creamy not
too hard so it's gonna be perfect.
Then I got some sourdough Look at this beauty We're gonna be making my favorite
fried tomato cheddar toast.
This is one of my favorite things to make in the summer and it's so
easy and I can't believe I haven't made it yet because I've just been so
busy.
It was another one of those things on my list but all you have to
do is get some good crispy fresh bread.
It has to be.
You drizzle some olive oil in a pan and you toast the bread on both
sides until it gets nice and toasty and browned.
Then you rub a garlic clove all over the bread to give it that garlicky
taste I like a lot on mine, but do what works for you.
And then we crumbled that cheddar, put it on top.
We sliced those beautiful tomatoes.
I like a thick slice.
The thicker, the better, in my opinion.
Added a little bit of salt, a little bit of pepper, and decided to also
add some chopped chives since they were just in my fridge.
You have seen prettier toasts because I would not believe you.
it's just perfect
we just got ready to go have dinner
and we were gonna cook at home i was gonna make a whole recipe a
whole thing but then this happened and we're gonna go celebrate
i reached 500 000 subscribers today um i don't want to be that person that's
like oh my god thank you so much but also like if you're watching this
whenever you're watching it i appreciate you if you subscribed if you've watched even one
video even clicked on one video didn't even watch it i still appreciate you um
and i mean this is crazy because yonyo was just telling me that he somewhere
has a screenshot of my profile when i only had a hundred subscribers my first
video on youtube was on september 18th 2020 so september of this year coming up
i will literally have done this for four years which is crazy so i'm just
really appreciative and we're gonna go get some food to eat a little bite and
then drink some wine and yeah just have a little moment of gratitude and how
do we feel about how do we feel about these summer sandals these ones with
socks for for like fall i don't know about it but it's dark so nobody
can see it anyways the only thing i want to say is that i'm super
proud of you and I will find that picture and I think it's in my
phone where you have like 100 subscribers I remember we were watching it oh we
were watching it go from 99 to 100 yes it's crazy I'm going to have
to find it yeah well
well here we are guys here we are guys
for
breakfast this morning i was feeling a little bit lazy and i just wanted something
simple so i had some cherries going in a pan with a little bit of
maple syrup to make that same sauce and then scooped some yogurt into a bowl
added the stewed up warmed up cherries on top some days are just simple like
this and i don't make anything too complicated or fancy or complex especially because i
wanted to get out of the house and go grab a little treat This
is my Sunday
ritual.
I just got to Domino Park here in Williamsburg after going to Greenpoint to stop
at a radio bakery and I got a ham and butter baguette.
It's actually kind of hot right now, but it also feels like it's about to
rain and I'm pretty sure it's going to rain.
So I'm not going to be here for too long, but this view, do you
see it?
I love this park so much.
It's right by the water, and it's so nice and quiet.
I'm just going to eat my sandwich and read my book for a little bit
if I can find a spot.
and finally for dinner we are making some japanese sweet potatoes just puncture the skin
with a fork wrap it up in a tin foil and then you put it
at 450 degrees for about an hour so i got started on those early and
then when they were ready i started making some steak for yoni and i that's
not all for me.
I seasoned it with some random seasonings, cooked it about you know medium, medium rare
and I started making a little green salad with that same dressing that I had
in my fridge.
I love a crispy green salad.
It makes for the perfect side especially when you have stronger in flavor items like
steak and sweet potatoes and I also decided to make a little burrata and tomato
plate and then we plated everything.
I like to mash up my sweet potato a little bit and then add some
butter on top and it melts into the potato more and always add salt and
pepper to the sweet potato because it's so sweet it needs that balance but then
i decided to go crazy and add that hot honey from trader joe's right on
top and that's pretty much it for this video this meal was a 10 out
of 10 always hits the spot let me know if you guys try any of
the recipes um excuse my reactions i'm always so extra but i just love food
so much i hope you guys enjoyed this video and end up making some of
these recipes and i'll see you guys next week